Register of the Fenton Stratton Jacobs papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Fenton Stratton Jacobs papers
1910-1964
66022
Hoover Institution Archives
15 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box, 1 oversize folder (7.9 linear feet)
Correspondence, writings, printed matter, maps, and photographs relating to cavalry tactics, logistics, and military transportation during and after World Wars I and II.
Jacobs, Fenton Stratton, 1892-1966.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1966.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the library catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
Fenton Stratton Jacobs was born on April 17, 1892, in Gordonsville, Virginia. He began his military career in 1909 as a member of the Ancient and Honorable Richmond, Virginia Light Infantry Blues Battalion. In May of 1917 he was appointed a second lieutenant of cavalry and received his commission in the regular army on October 25, 1917. That same month Jacobs was transferred to France with the 3rd United States Cavalry. He was later named aide-de-camp to Brigadier General Charles Gerhardt, with whom he served in the 7th Base Section, 35th and 92nd Infantry Divisions. From December 1918 to May 1919, he commanded Hq. Troop, 89th Infantry Division, in Germany.
When Jacobs returned to the United States, he was identified with various cavalry regiments and attended service schools. He served for two years on the faculty of The Cavalry School. During this period, he authored and illustrated a text book, Cavalry Combat, based on an historical study of world-wide cavalry operations in World War I. Jacobs was assigned to the office Chief of Cavalry and General Headquarters, War College, Washington D.C., and during this time was editor of The Cavalry Journal from 1940 until 1942.
During World War II, Jacobs served as Chief of Staff of the 91st Infantry Division for one year, and was transferred to the European Theater in July 1943. In England, after a brief service in G-3 GHQ, he commanded the Western Base Section in England until August 1944, when he established and commanded Channel Base Section in France until after VE-Day.
On June 20, 1945, Jacobs was transferred to the Philippine Islands, and there commanded Base M, in Northern Luzon, until December 1945. When he returned to the United States, he commanded the Seattle Port of Embarkation for one year, then served as Deputy Commander and Commander at the San Francisco Port of Embarkation until 1949. Jacobs then returned to the Seattle Port of Embarkation, to serve as Commanding General until 1952, when he retired to Pebble Beach, California. He died in 1966.
Jacobs was awarded the Distinguished Service Medal, Legion of Merit with Oak Leaf Cluster, and the Bronze Star Medal. His foreign decorations include the French Legion of Honor in the grade of Chevalier, and the Croix de Guerre with Palm, the Commander of the British Empire, and the Belgian Order of Leopold II in the grade of Commander. He was a member of the Scabbard and Blade Military Fraternity.
Scope and Content of Collection
This collection documents the career of Brigadier General Fenton Stratton Jacobs during and immediately after World War II. It contains personal and professional correspondence primarily dating from 1944 to 1952, maps, and newspapers. The bulk of the collection relates to Jacobs’ experiences in the military while stationed in England, France, and the Philippines, as well as his role as the Commanding Officer at the San Francisco and Seattle Ports of Embarkation. The collection touches on his efforts to develop amicable relationships between the French and American military, as well as the activities of the American military during the period following the close of the World War II, with emphasis on the Seattle and San Francisco ports. The collection also contains newspaper articles, yearbooks, other printed matter, and photos documenting his early military career in the Richmond Blues and his activities as a cavalry officer.
United States. Army--Officers.; United States. Army--Transport service..; Cavalry.; World War, 1914-1918--Transportation.; World War, 1939-1945--Transportation.
- Biographical File, 1912-1952
  - Cavalry journals, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Cavalry School yearbooks, 1921-1924 (Box-folder 1: 2-5)
  - Commendation in Recognition of Leadership, 1952 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Department of Defense Office of Public Information biography, 1951 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Newspaper articles from Lille, France, 1945 (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Personal files, 1943-1951 (Box-folder 1: 9, 2: 1-3)
    Scope and Contents note
    Files created by Jacobs containing biographical documents, correspondence, memoranda, and printed matter, arranged chronologically.
  - Recommendation for Award of Oak-Leaf Cluster to the Legion of Merit, 1945 April 14 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Richmond Blues scrapbook, 1912 (Box-folder 2: 5)
- Correspondence, 1944-1952
  - 1944
    - American Red Cross in Great Britain and Western Europe (Box-folder 2: 6)
    - Anderson, K. A. N. (Box-folder 2: 7)
    - Andrus, Barton C. (Box-folder 2: 8)
    - Balding, A. S. (Box-folder 2: 9)
    - Bell, Frank F. (Box-folder 2: 10)
    - Betts, Ed. C. (Box-folder 2: 11)
    - Bissell, Clayton (Box-folder 2: 12)
    - le Blanc (Box-folder 2: 13)
    - Bunting, Brian (Box-folder 2: 14)
    - Casalis, Henri A. (Box-folder 2: 15)
    - Christian, George Watson (Box-folder 2: 16)
    - Closon, F. (Box-folder 2: 17)
    - Craig, Harry N. (Box-folder 2: 18)
    - Cunningham, Alan G. (Box-folder 2: 19)
    - Deligne (Box-folder 2: 20)
    - Duffie, Harold R. (Box-folder 2: 21)
    - Faure, André (Box-folder 2: 22)
    - Febiger, Paul (Box-folder 2: 23)
    - Franey, James M. (Box-folder 2: 24)
    - Fuerster, Hervey A. (Box-folder 2: 25)
    - Giard, Jacques (Box-folder 2: 26)
    - Granger, H. R. (Box-folder 2: 27)
    - Granger, Judie (Box-folder 2: 28)
    - Gullat, Doswell (Box-folder 2: 29)
    - Hawarden (Box-folder 2: 30)
    - Headquarters, Channel Base Section, European Theater of Operations (Box-folder 2: 31)
    - Isakson (Box-folder 2: 32)
    - Jackson, Harold R. (Box-folder 2: 33)
    - Lee, John C. H. (Box-folder 2: 34)
    - Leslie, J. T. (Box-folder 2: 35)
    - Littlejohn, Robert M. (Box-folder 2: 36)
    - Lord, R. B. (Box-folder 2: 37)
    - Maillot, R. (Box-folder 3: 1)
    - Mayor of Lille (Cabinet du Maire) (Box-folder 3: 2)
    - Mayor of St. Addresse (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - McCabe, Hilton H. (Box-folder 3: 4)
    - McKenzie (Box-folder 3: 5)
    - McMicking, Neil (Box-folder 3: 6)
    - McWilliams, R. A. (Box-folder 3: 7)
    - Meyer, Fred A. (Box-folder 3: 8)
    - Miller, Bill (Box-folder 3: 9)
    - Morgan, W. D. (Box-folder 3: 10)
    - Morris, E. L. (Box-folder 3: 11)
    - Olander, George L. (Box-folder 3: 12)
    - Plank, Ewart G. (Box-folder 3: 13)
    - Le Président du Comité Local de la Libération Nationale (Box-folder 3: 14)
    - Pulling, Lewis A. (Box-folder 3: 15)
    - Puntenney, William H. (Box-folder 3: 16)
    - Renfroe, D. J. (Box-folder 3: 17)
    - Rogers, C. Bolles (Box-folder 3: 18)
    - Ross, Frank S. (Box-folder 3: 19)
    - Rumbough, W. S. (Box-folder 3: 20)
    - Searight, William (Box-folder 3: 21)
    - Shaw, Carl R. (Box-folder 3: 22)
    - Shirk, George H. (Box-folder 3: 23)
    - Slaughter, P. H. (Box-folder 3: 24)
    - Smith, Fred E. (Box-folder 3: 25)
    - Taylor, Henry M. (Box-folder 3: 26)
    - Thorn, Gordon L. (Box-folder 3: 27)
    - Thorne, Andrew N. (Box-folder 3: 28)
    - Toumey, William H. (Box-folder 3: 29)
    - Vaughan, H. B. (Box-folder 3: 30)
    - Verlomme, Roger (Box-folder 3: 31)
    - Watkins, John B. (Box-folder 3: 32)
    - Watson, W. G. (Box-folder 3: 33)
    - Wilkes, John (Box-folder 3: 34)
    - Wilson, Arthur R. (Box-folder 3: 35)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 3: 36)
  - 1945
    - Anderson, Sarah (Box-folder 3: 37)
    - Arenz, A. H. (Box-folder 3: 38)
    - Arnold, Robert H. (Box-folder 3: 39)
    - Axelrad, A. J. (Box-folder 3: 40)
    - Barksdale, James A. (Box-folder 3: 41)
    - Bernard-Ernoult, P. (Box-folder 3: 42)
    - Channel Base Section Headquarters (Box-folder 3: 43)
    - Clark, H. L. (Box-folder 3: 44)
    - Clark, Mark W. (Box-folder 3: 45)
    - Clark, W. (Box-folder 3: 46)
    - Closon, F. (Box-folder 3: 47)
    - Closoy, Z. L. (Box-folder 3: 48)
    - Code, James A. (Box-folder 3: 49)
    - Commanding Officer and Staff, Belgium Leave Station, U.S. Army (Box-folder 3: 50)
    - Commissaire Délégué (Box-folder 3: 51)
    - Commité Polonais de Libération Nationale (Box-folder 3: 52)
    - Consul generale de Pologne (Box-folder 3: 53)
    - Coyle, Wilbur F. (Box-folder 3: 54)
    - Delannoy, M. A. (Box-folder 3: 55)
    - Deligne (Box-folder 3: 56)
    - Département du Nord Arrondissement de Lille (Box-folder 3: 57)
    - Departmental Association of War Prisoners of the Nord (Box-folder 3: 58)
    - Diligent, Felix (Box-folder 3: 59)
    - Director of the Social Service of French Army, 1st Region (Box-folder 3: 60)
    - Donaldson, William H. (Box-folder 3: 61)
    - Dunn, William Mck. (Box-folder 3: 62)
    - European Theatre of Operations (Box-folder 3: 63)
    - Forsythe, Edward C. (Box-folder 3: 64)
    - French Welcome Association (Box-folder 3: 65)
    - French Welcome Committee, Roubaix (Box-folder 3: 66)
    - Gaston, M. Macre (Box-folder 3: 67)
    - Gerhardt, Charles (Box-folder 3: 68)
    - Gill, Joseph (Box-folder 3: 69)
    - The Girls' Home (Box-folder 3: 70)
    - Governor of Liège (Box-folder 3: 71)
    - Granger, Hugh R. (Box-folder 3: 72)
    - Guinan, Gladys (Box-folder 3: 73)
    - Gullatt, Doswell (Box-folder 3: 74)
    - Hennegueline, Henri (Box-folder 3: 75)
    - Hughes, E. S. (Box-folder 3: 76)
    - Isear, Ann E. (Box-folder 3: 77)
    - Kendall, Paul G. (Box-folder 3: 78)
    - Leavey, Jean (Box-folder 3: 79)
    - Leclercq, Joseph (Box-folder 3: 80)
    - Lee, John C. H. (Box-folder 3: 81)
    - Littlejohn, Robert M. (Box-folder 3: 82)
    - Lord, R. B., Headquarters, Channel Base Section (Box-folder 3: 83)
    - Lyons, V. (Box-folder 3: 84)
    - M., Tom J. (Box-folder 3: 85)
    - Maignan, M. E. (Box-folder 3: 86)
    - Marchetti, Augustus A. (Box-folder 3: 87)
    - McCormick, W. J. (Box-folder 3: 88)
    - McMicking, Neil (Box-folder 3: 89)
    - Newbury, T. G. (Box-folder 3: 90)
    - Parmenter, R. H. R. (Box-folder 3: 91)
    - Pasquesoone, Maurice (Box-folder 3: 92)
    - Philips, Joseph L. (Box-folder 4: 1)
    - Pire, N. (Box-folder 4: 2)
    - Plank, Ewart G. (Box-folder 4: 3)
    - Poland, Consulate General (Box-folder 4: 4)
    - Potie, Jacques (Box-folder 4: 5)
    - Rapport, V. A. (Box-folder 4: 6)
    - Regional Commissioner of the Republic in Rouen (Box-folder 4: 7)
    - Regional Director of Information, Lille (Box-folder 4: 8)
    - Robichez, M. (Box-folder 4: 9)
    - Rogers, Pleas B. (Box-folder 4: 10)
    - Scanlan, David B. (Box-folder 4: 11)
    - Segard (Box-folder 4: 12)
    - Sherman, John B. (Box-folder 4: 13)
    - Shuman, Leigh D. (Box-folder 4: 14)
    - Surtees, G. (Box-folder 4: 15)
    - Union of the Résistance (Box-folder 4: 16)
    - Verlomme (Box-folder 4: 17)
    - Verstraete (Box-folder 4: 18)
    - Vice President of Municipal Delegation of Lille (Box-folder 4: 19)
    - Watkins, John B. (Box-folder 4: 20)
    - Whitcomb, Richard S. (Box-folder 4: 21)
    - 210th MP Company (Box-folder 4: 22)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 4: 23)
  - 1946
    - Arbuthnott, Hugh (Box-folder 4: 24)
    - Arends, Henry (Box-folder 4: 25)
    - Barkhurst, G. L. (Box-folder 4: 26)
    - Barrett, Edward T. (Box-folder 4: 27)
    - Berg, Sexton (Box-folder 4: 28)
    - Bethune, P. H. (Box-folder 4: 29)
    - Blake, R. L. (Box-folder 4: 30)
    - Broadus, W. M. (Box-folder 4: 31)
    - Buell, Noble E. (Box-folder 4: 32)
    - Byers, Clovis E. (Box-folder 4: 33)
    - Campbell, Harold H. (Box-folder 4: 34)
    - Collector of Internal Revenue (Box-folder 4: 35)
    - Crothers, Alex J. (Box-folder 4: 36)
    - Curley, Frank (Box-folder 4: 37)
    - Cutchins, John A. (Box-folder 4: 38)
    - Delmer (Box-folder 4: 39)
    - Descamps, Edouard (Box-folder 4: 40)
    - DeWitt, Wilmer W. (Box-folder 4: 41)
    - Duin, Robert (Box-folder 4: 42)
    - E., N. (Box-folder 4: 43)
    - Eastwood, Harold H. (Box-folder 4: 44)
    - Escobosa, Hector (Box-folder 4: 45)
    - Eulau, Milton Bernard (Box-folder 4: 46)
    - Fairgrave, D. J. (Box-folder 4: 47)
    - Faure, Andre (Box-folder 4: 48)
    - Foote, William Cooper (Box-folder 4: 49)
    - Forsythe, Edward C. (Box-folder 4: 50)
    - Gerhardt, Charles H. (Box-folder 4: 51)
    - Giard, Jacques E. (Box-folder 4: 52)
    - Granger, H. R. (Box-folder 4: 53)
    - Guinau, Gladys (Box-folder 4: 54)
    - Herr, Frederick (Box-folder 4: 55)
    - Jones, R. E. (Box-folder 4: 56)
    - Kohler, A. W. (Box-folder 4: 57)
    - Lash, Fred H. (Box-folder 4: 58)
    - Leavey, Edmund H. (Box-folder 4: 59)
    - Lee, Can (Box-folder 4: 60)
    - Lee, John H. C. (Box-folder 4: 61)
    - Linney, Elizabeth (Box-folder 4: 62)
    - Llewellyn, E. M. (Box-folder 4: 63)
    - Macauley, T. C. (Box-folder 4: 64)
    - Marquis, A. N. (Box-folder 4: 65)
    - McKay, Neal H. (Box-folder 4: 66)
    - McKinsey, Cecil (Box-folder 4: 67)
    - Montgomery, R. S. (Box-folder 4: 68)
    - Parker, Paul E. (Box-folder 4: 69)
    - Peiree, C. T. (Box-folder 4: 70)
    - Pittman, L. C. (Box-folder 4: 71)
    - Quinn, James B. (Box-folder 4: 72)
    - Reynolds, R. B. (Box-folder 4: 73)
    - Ring, Edward H. (Box-folder 4: 74)
    - Ringenburg, M. G. (Box-folder 4: 75)
    - Rome, Sol (Box-folder 4: 76)
    - Rydbom, Stanley W. (Box-folder 4: 77)
    - Schick, L. E. (Box-folder 4: 78)
    - Snider, Henry F. (Box-folder 4: 79)
    - Stewart, George C. (Box-folder 4: 80)
    - Stott, Ken W. (Box-folder 4: 81)
    - Stratton, M. A. (Box-folder 4: 82)
    - Swope, Gordon (Box-folder 4: 83)
    - Taeni, Selma (Box-folder 4: 84)
    - Vaughan, H. E. (Box-folder 4: 85)
    - Williams, Ernest A. (Box-folder 4: 86)
    - Wright, Denny (Box-folder 4: 87)
    - Wylie, Robert H. (Box-folder 4: 88)
    - Young, M. C. (Box-folder 4: 89)
  - 1947
    - Bowman, Frederick C. (Box-folder 5: 1)
    - Brown, Harley D. (Box-folder 5: 2)
    - Bunting, G. C. (Box-folder 5: 3)
    - Byers, C. E. (Box-folder 5: 4)
    - Coleson, C. V. (Box-folder 5: 5)
    - Collector of Internal Revenue (Box-folder 5: 6)
    - Compton, William R. (Box-folder 5: 7)
    - DeWitt, Calvin (Box-folder 5: 8)
    - Donaldson, William H. (Box-folder 5: 9)
    - Duffie, Harold R. (Box-folder 5: 10)
    - Eastwood, Harold E. (Box-folder 5: 11)
    - Eulau, Milton Bernard (Box-folder 5: 12)
    - Faure, André (Box-folder 5: 13)
    - Foote, William Cooper (Box-folder 5: 14)
    - Gaffney, John (Box-folder 5: 15)
    - Giard, Jacques E. (Box-folder 5: 16)
    - Glasgow, J. M. (Box-folder 5: 17)
    - Gordon, R. A. (Box-folder 5: 18)
    - Granger, Judie (Box-folder 5: 19)
    - Gullatt, Doswell (Box-folder 5: 20)
    - Hamer, Marjorie (Box-folder 5: 21)
    - Heard, J. W. (Box-folder 5: 22)
    - Heileman, Frank A. (Box-folder 5: 23)
    - Heizer, J. H. (Box-folder 5: 24)
    - Herr, Frederick (Box-folder 5: 25)
    - Hull, J. E. (Box-folder 5: 26)
    - Isakson (Box-folder 5: 27)
    - Jennings, Leslie H. (Box-folder 5: 28)
    - Kavanaugh, Kathy (Box-folder 5: 29)
    - Kells, C. H. (Box-folder 5: 30)
    - Kendall, Paul G. (Box-folder 5: 31)
    - Keyser, George V. (Box-folder 5: 32)
    - Kojassar, A. (Box-folder 5: 33)
    - Krumm, Jeannette F. (Box-folder 5: 34)
    - Langley, Charles F. (Box-folder 5: 35)
    - Larr, Marjory K. (Box-folder 5: 36)
    - Lastayo, Edward H. (Box-folder 5: 37)
    - Lattimore, Walter C. (Box-folder 5: 38)
    - Leavey, Edmond A. (Box-folder 5: 39)
    - Lee, Can (Box-folder 5: 40)
    - Lee, John C. H. (Box-folder 5: 41)
    - Lewis, Willis R. (Box-folder 5: 42)
    - Llewelyn, John (Box-folder 5: 43)
    - Maas, Harry (Box-folder 5: 44)
    - MacNabb, Alexander B. (Box-folder 5: 45)
    - Malm, Pierre (Box-folder 5: 46)
    - McKay (Box-folder 5: 47)
    - Montgomery Ward & Co. (Box-folder 5: 48)
    - Myers, Norman C. (Box-folder 5: 49)
    - Parker, Paul B. (Box-folder 5: 50)
    - Paxson, George E. (Box-folder 5: 51)
    - Pells, Phyllis (Box-folder 5: 52)
    - Philpot, E. W. (Box-folder 5: 53)
    - Plank, Ewart G. (Box-folder 5: 54)
    - Quinn, James B. (Box-folder 5: 55)
    - Rabb, William E. (Box-folder 5: 56)
    - Rehm, Harold W. (Box-folder 5: 57)
    - Rice, Charles (Box-folder 5: 58)
    - Ring, Edward H. (Box-folder 5: 59)
    - Rogers, C. Lanore (Box-folder 5: 60)
    - Rubin, Samuel (Box-folder 5: 61)
    - Searles, J. L. (Box-folder 5: 62)
    - Sears Roebuck (Box-folder 5: 63)
    - Shambora, William E. (Box-folder 5: 64)
    - Shand, Arthur T. (Box-folder 5: 65)
    - Shaver, Robert T. (Box-folder 5: 66)
    - Sheldon, Charles A. (Box-folder 5: 67)
    - Smith, C. D. (Box-folder 5: 68)
    - Smith, Kenneth I. (Box-folder 5: 69)
    - Smith, Wayne C. (Box-folder 5: 70)
    - Stanley, Joseph K. (Box-folder 5: 71)
    - Stead, George (Box-folder 5: 72)
    - Stewart, G. C. (Box-folder 5: 73)
    - Stoddard, C. S. (Box-folder 5: 74)
    - Stott, Ken W. (Box-folder 5: 75)
    - Stratton, L. C. (Box-folder 5: 76)
    - Styer, W. D. (Box-folder 5: 77)
    - Sullivan, E. W. (Box-folder 5: 78)
    - Swope, John G. (Box-folder 5: 79)
    - Tapner, John (Box-folder 5: 80)
    - Townsend, W. D. (Box-folder 5: 81)
    - Vaughan, H. B. (Box-folder 5: 82)
    - Wagner, John G. (Box-folder 5: 83)
    - Walker, I. G. (Box-folder 5: 84)
    - Walther, Norris E. (Box-folder 5: 85)
    - Witherell, Thelma E. (Box-folder 5: 86)
    - Woodworth, W. D. (Box-folder 5: 87)
    - Wyman, W. D. (Box-folder 5: 88)
    - Yount, Paul (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - 1948
    - San Francisco departure party invitations (Box-folder 6: 2)
    - Abel, Arthur H. (Box-folder 6: 3)
    - Anderson, G. A. M. (Box-folder 6: 4)
    - Arbuthnott, Hugh (Box-folder 6: 5)
    - Army Advisory Committee (Box-folder 6: 6)
    - Army Transportation Agency (Box-folder 6: 7)
    - Atterbury, Logan C. (Box-folder 6: 8)
    - Bannick, John H. (Box-folder 6: 9)
    - Bare, G. H. (Box-folder 6: 10)
    - Barret, E. T. (Box-folder 6: 11)
    - Barth, George H. (Box-folder 6: 12)
    - Batcheller, Henry Irving (Box-folder 6: 13)
    - Baxter, George B. (Box-folder 6: 14)
    - Beaudoin, William W. (Box-folder 6: 15)
    - Beck, Vancel R. (Box-folder 6: 16)
    - Bellero, Rinaldo (Box-folder 6: 17)
    - Bethune, P. H. (Box-folder 6: 18)
    - Black, William B. (Box-folder 6: 19)
    - Blount, Roy E. (Box-folder 6: 20)
    - Boon (Box-folder 6: 21)
    - Bradford, W. B. (Box-folder 6: 22)
    - Brigadier, Mort (Box-folder 6: 23)
    - British Consulate General (Box-folder 6: 24)
    - Bryan, F. G. (Box-folder 6: 25)
    - Bunting, Lloyd (Box-folder 6: 26)
    - Bush, Stanley T. R. (Box-folder 6: 27)
    - Byers, Clovis E. (Box-folder 6: 28)
    - Carmel Realty Co. (Box-folder 6: 29)
    - Carr, William S. (Box-folder 6: 30)
    - Cassidy, John F. (Box-folder 6: 31)
    - Cavender, Charles C. (Box-folder 6: 32)
    - Clark, Mark W. (Box-folder 6: 33)
    - Collector of Internal Revenue (Box-folder 6: 34)
    - Commanding General, Fort Stotsenburg (Box-folder 6: 35)
    - Commanding General, San Francisco Port of Embarkation (Box-folder 6: 36)
    - Conner, Raymond T. (Box-folder 6: 37)
    - Connor, Edward H. (Box-folder 6: 38)
    - Conrad, Bryan (Box-folder 6: 39)
    - Crawford, Robert F. (Box-folder 6: 40)
    - Crawford, Wilson (Box-folder 6: 41)
    - Cress, Cornelia V. N. (Box-folder 6: 42)
    - Crothers, J. A. (Box-folder 6: 43)
    - Davidson, Garrison H. (Box-folder 6: 44)
    - Dean, Blanche L. (Box-folder 6: 45)
    - Degen, Frank (Box-folder 6: 46)
    - DeWitt, Wilmar W. (Box-folder 6: 47)
    - Dissinger, Charles E. (Box-folder 6: 48)
    - Donaldson, W. H. (Box-folder 6: 49)
    - Duffie, Harold R. (Box-folder 6: 50)
    - Eastwood, H. E. (Box-folder 6: 51)
    - Eddy, Crowell D. (Box-folder 6: 52)
    - Eichelberger, R. L. (Box-folder 6: 53)
    - Elliott, R. H. (Box-folder 6: 54)
    - Elliott, Wilbur S. (Box-folder 6: 55)
    - Fall, Arch (Box-folder 6: 56)
    - Far East Command, General Headquarters (Box-folder 6: 57)
    - Feldman, H. (Box-folder 6: 58)
    - Finn, Earl (Box-folder 6: 59)
    - Fortier, M. V. (Box-folder 6: 60)
    - Foster, George L. (Box-folder 6: 61)
    - Fowler, Ann (Box-folder 6: 62)
    - French Consul (Box-folder 6: 63)
    - Fuller, Lottie M. (Box-folder 6: 64)
    - Giard, Jacques E. (Box-folder 6: 65)
    - Gilmore, Robert M. (Box-folder 6: 66)
    - Graham, Walter F. (Box-folder 6: 67)
    - Greenhaw, Anthony (Box-folder 6: 68)
    - Guerrero, Josefina N. (Box-folder 6: 69)
    - Harris, J. T. (Box-folder 6: 70)
    - Hart, Harry L. (Box-folder 6: 71)
    - Hayden, F. L. (Box-folder 6: 72)
    - Heard, J. W. (Box-folder 6: 73)
    - Heileman, F. A. (Box-folder 6: 74)
    - Hellman, Francis W. (Box-folder 6: 75)
    - Herlihy, Marion (Box-folder 6: 76)
    - Herr, Frederick (Box-folder 6: 77)
    - Hoffman, Eugene F. (Box-folder 6: 78)
    - Horsman, E. W. (Box-folder 6: 79)
    - Howe, H. D. (Box-folder 6: 80)
    - Hughes, Lloyd B. (Box-folder 6: 81)
    - Humphries, O. W. (Box-folder 6: 82)
    - Hunt, LeRoy P. (Box-folder 6: 83)
    - Hutchison, C. R. (Box-folder 6: 84)
    - Hutchinson, Clifton C. (Box-folder 6: 85)
    - Hutson, R. K. (Box-folder 6: 86)
    - Johnson, Harold B. (Box-folder 6: 87)
    - Jones, Earnest W. (Box-folder 6: 88)
    - Jones, R. E. (Box-folder 7: 1)
    - Judd, John H. (Box-folder 7: 2)
    - Kavanaugh, Kathryn (Box-folder 7: 3)
    - Kendall, Paul (Box-folder 7: 4)
    - Killion, George (Box-folder 7: 5)
    - Kleinman (Box-folder 7: 6)
    - Knizek, Joe (Box-folder 7: 7)
    - Kreuter, Elizabether Howe (Box-folder 7: 8)
    - Lafayette College (Box-folder 7: 9)
    - Langley, Charles (Box-folder 7: 10)
    - Larr (Box-folder 7: 11)
    - Laughlin, Sibyl March (Box-folder 7: 12)
    - Leavey, Edmond H. (Box-folder 7: 13)
    - Lee, Can (Box-folder 7: 14)
    - Lee, John C. H. (Box-folder 7: 15)
    - de Lein, Reinhold (Box-folder 7: 16)
    - Lester, J. A. (Box-folder 7: 17)
    - Lowe, H. A. (Box-folder 7: 18)
    - MacNabb, Alexander B. (Box-folder 7: 19)
    - Manufacturers Life Insurance Co. (Box-folder 7: 20)
    - Marcus, M. H. (Box-folder 7: 21)
    - de la Mare, A. J. (Box-folder 7: 22)
    - Marks, John W. (Box-folder 7: 23)
    - Marriott, Owen R. (Box-folder 7: 24)
    - Marsh, M. W. (Box-folder 7: 25)
    - Mast, Fred E. (Box-folder 7: 26)
    - May, J. G. (Box-folder 7: 27)
    - McAuliffe, Regina A. (Box-folder 7: 28)
    - McCarthy, E. B. (Box-folder 7: 29)
    - McConnell, F. (Box-folder 7: 30)
    - McKay, Neal E. (Box-folder 7: 31)
    - Miller, Harold (Box-folder 7: 32)
    - Minier, Earl F. (Box-folder 7: 33)
    - Moore, George F. (Box-folder 7: 34)
    - Muhlenburg, John C. R. (Box-folder 7: 35)
    - Newman, A. F. (Box-folder 7: 36)
    - Norgaard, Alfred R. (Box-folder 7: 37)
    - Office of the Adjutant General, Department of the Army (Box-folder 7: 38)